<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="http://brightskypress.com/wp-content/book-samples/style_xml.css" ?>

<productListing title="Arte Público Books">
  <product>
    <coverimage><image href="https://artepublicopress.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/Brujas-lechuzas-y-espantos.jpg"/></coverimage>
    <name>Witches, Owls and Spooks</name>
    <author>Alonso Perales</author>
    <isbn>978-1-55885-512-0</isbn>
    <grade>G3-G5</grade>
    <cost>$4.98</cost>
    <description>Brujas, lechuzas y espantos: In this bilingual collection of five stories, Don Cecilio tells the neighborhood children stories that make their hair stand on end. &quot;In my barrio they told the story…&quot; and so his cuento would begin. In &quot;The Owl and the Bundle,&quot; young Tomas disappears without a trace. Distraught, his parents and siblings look for him everywhere with no luck. Upon returning home, his father sees something curious, an owl flying above the house carrying a bundle with its talons. &quot;Is it possible,&quot; he wonders, &quot;that the bundle is Little Tomas?&quot; Could the owl have taken their precious son?</description>
    <ar_points></ar_points>
  </product>
  <product>
    <coverimage><image href="https://artepublicopress.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/Case-of-the-Pen-Gone-Missing-The.jpg"/></coverimage>
    <name>The Case of the Pen Gone Missing: A Mickey Rangel Mystery</name>
    <author>René Saldaña, Jr.</author>
    <isbn>978-1-55885-555-7</isbn>
    <grade>G3-G5</grade>
    <cost>$4.98</cost>
    <description>El caso de la pluma perdida: Colección Mickey Rangel, detective privado: Rumor has it that Toots stole Eddy's pen. It's not just any old pen; it's his dad's pen. It has the White House logo on it. Eddy's father, a senator from South Texas, got the pen from the President of the United States when he visited the White House last year. As Mickey begins his investigation, though, all the clues point to Toots and her newly ex-boyfriend as the primary suspects.</description>
    <ar_points>1</ar_points>
  </product>
  <product>
    <coverimage><image href="https://artepublicopress.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/Family-Familia.jpg"/></coverimage>
    <name>Family</name>
    <author>Diane Gonzales Bertrand</author>
    <isbn>978-1-55885-270-9</isbn>
    <grade>PreK-G2</grade>
    <cost>$3.98</cost>
    <description>Familia: Young Daniel doesn't share his dad's excitement over going to a family reunion. What's the big deal? After all, it's just going to be a bunch of old people he doesn't know, sitting around telling stories about other old people he doesn't know. Once there, though, Daniel is in for several pleasant surprises—and a happy discovery about the meaning of family, familia.</description>
    <ar_points>0.5</ar_points>
  </product>
  <product>
    <coverimage><image href="https://artepublicopress.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/Frog-and-His-Friends-The.jpg"/></coverimage>
    <name>Frog and His Friends Save Humanity</name>
    <author>Victor Villaseñor</author>
    <isbn>978-1-55885-556-4</isbn>
    <grade>G3-G5</grade>
    <cost>$3.98</cost>
    <description>La rana y sus amigos salvan a la humanidad: It's the Spring of Creation, and all of the animals are busy doing what they do best.&#160; There was no confusion.&#160; But suddenly, a strange, furless, shell-less creature appears in their midst and the animals are mystified by the strange being.&#160; The bear knew that this creature would not be as strong, the deer knew it would not be as fast, and even the grasshopper knew it was not going to hop and screech like him.  What follows is a raucous debate about what to do with the helpless being.&#160; Eat the creature?&#160; Defend the creature?&#160; Leave it to fend for itself in the forest?&#160; The fate of humanity rests in the paws and wings of the animal community.</description>
    <ar_points>0.5</ar_points>
  </product>
  <product>
    <coverimage><image href="https://artepublicopress.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/icy-watermelon.jpg"/></coverimage>
    <name>Icy Watermelon</name>
    <author>Mary Sue Galindo</author>
    <isbn>978-1-55885-307-2</isbn>
    <grade>PreK-G2</grade>
    <cost>$3.98</cost>
    <description>Sandía fría: Family gatherings often promise to be fruitful for grandkids, but they generally don't offer much in the way of surprises. When the charming family at the center of Icy Watermelon / Sandía fría gathers to enjoy a watermelon and some family fun, they find that even something so simple can create a treat that the whole family enjoys.</description>
    <ar_points>0.5</ar_points>
  </product>
  <product>
    <coverimage><image href="https://artepublicopress.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/Last-Doll-The.jpg"/></coverimage>
    <name>The Last Doll</name>
    <author>Diane Gonzales Bertrand</author>
    <isbn>978-1-55885-291-4</isbn>
    <grade>G3-G5</grade>
    <cost>$3.98</cost>
    <description>La última muñeca: Toys today can walk and talk, run and jump, boom and vroom, glow and crow. So how is a classy doll in a room full of robots to compete?</description>
    <ar_points>0.5</ar_points>
  </product>
  <product>
    <coverimage><image href="https://artepublicopress.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/Missing-Chancleta-The-NEW.jpg"/></coverimage>
    <name>The Missing Chancleta and Other Top-Secret Cases</name>
    <author>Alidis Vicente</author>
    <isbn>978-1-55885-779-7</isbn>
    <grade>G3-G5</grade>
    <cost>$4.98</cost>
    <description>La chancleta perdida y otros casos secretos: The beautiful but old-fashioned Sarita sadly watches as her shelf-mates are purchased by eager shoppers and taken home. She looks out through the dust-covered plastic of her box, and she worries that she will be the last one. Every day she preens and puts her best porcelain face forward, but every evening, she remains on the shelf.</description>
    <ar_points>1</ar_points>
  </product>
  <product>
    <coverimage><image href="https://artepublicopress.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/Monster-in-the-Mattress-The.jpg"/></coverimage>
    <name>The Monster in the Mattress and Other Stories</name>
    <author>Diane de Anda</author>
    <isbn>978-1-55885-693-6</isbn>
    <grade>G3-G5</grade>
    <cost>$4.98</cost>
    <description>El monstruo en el colchón y otros cuentos: Seven-year-old Rudi looks up to his big brother Tony, who isn't afraid to sleep in the dark. Tony humors Rudi, allowing him a night light next to his bed in the room they share especially after reading scary stories at bedtime. But when his bed starts shaking in the night, even brave Tony is sure a spooky creature has inhabited it. With their parents' help, the boys discover the real monster in the mattress is furry and has long ears!</description>
    <ar_points>1</ar_points>
  </product>
  <product>
    <coverimage><image href="https://artepublicopress.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/Muffler-Man1.jpg"/></coverimage>
    <name>Muffler Man</name>
    <author>Tito Campos</author>
    <isbn>978-1-55885-557-1</isbn>
    <grade>G3-G5</grade>
    <cost>$3.98</cost>
    <description>El hombre mofle: For the García family, leftovers provide the feast.&#160; Battered tin, pieces of metal, and scraps in a muffler shop inspire a young man and his family to believe in the American dream.  Young Chuy García longs to join his father, who has left Mexico in search of a better life for his family in the United States. To save money for the trip north, Chuy convinces his father's former employer at the local muffler shop to hire him to do odds and ends.&#160; There, Chuy learns something new about his father: he is the artist who made the Muffler Man, a metal statue that stands in front of the shop inviting customers inside.</description>
    <ar_points>0.5</ar_points>
  </product>
  <product>
    <coverimage><image href="https://artepublicopress.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/A-Mummy-in-Her-Backpack.jpg"/></coverimage>
    <name>A Mummy In Her Backpack</name>
    <author>James Luna</author>
    <isbn>978-1-55885-756-8</isbn>
    <grade>G3-G5</grade>
    <cost>$4.98</cost>
    <description>Una momia en su mochila: Flor enjoyed her two-week trip to Mexico, though she's glad to be back at school. But when she tries to pull her homework out of her backpack, she's shocked to feel a cold hand clutching hers. Thinking that the pesky boys in her class are playing a trick on her, she turns around to look into her pack. She's even more stunned when she sees two yellow eyes peeking out at her.</description>
    <ar_points>1</ar_points>
  </product>
  <product>
    <coverimage><image href="https://artepublicopress.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/Pepita-Takes-Time-Pepita-siempre-tardeHardcover.jpg"/></coverimage>
    <name>Pepita Takes Time</name>
    <author>Ofelia Dumas Lachtman</author>
    <isbn>978-1-55885-305-8</isbn>
    <grade>PreK-G2</grade>
    <cost>$8.48</cost>
    <description>Pepita, siempre tarde: But so what if she's a little late to breakfast . . . late to school . . . even late getting back home again? After all, Pepita thinks, that doesn't hurt anything, does it? But eventually Pepita learns from her best friend Sonya (introduced in Pepita Thinks Pink) that &quot;taking time&quot; can also mean taking time away from other people, and even cheating herself as well. And she finds that taking time may not be as much fun as sharing it with her family and friends.</description>
    <ar_points>0.5</ar_points>
  </product>
  <product>
    <coverimage><image href="https://artepublicopress.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/sip-slurp-soup-size-TEST.jpg"/></coverimage>
    <name>Sip, Slurp, Soup, Soup</name>
    <author>Diane Gonzales Bertrand</author>
    <isbn>978-1-55885-241-9</isbn>
    <grade>PreK-G2</grade>
    <cost>$3.98</cost>
    <description>Caldo, caldo, caldo: &quot;On rainy Sunday mornings when Mamá pulls out her tall, dark soup pot with tiny white spots, we know it will be a caldo day. Caldo, caldo, caldo.&quot; The kids know they are in for a special treat when Mamá begins preparing her delicious beef vegetable soup. Mamá's caldo &quot;fills up a warm spot inside us, and stops the sniffles, softens a cough, settles the stomach, and soothes a backache. It even massages tired feet!&quot;</description>
    <ar_points>0.5</ar_points>
  </product>
</productListing>
