<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="http://brightskypress.com/wp-content/book-samples/style_xml.css" ?>

<productListing title="LongTale Books">
  <product>
    <coverimage><image href="http://longtalepublishing.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/Little-Miss-Molly_cvr_300dpi-1024x1024.jpg"/></coverimage>
    <name>Little Miss Molly </name>
    <author>Melissa M. Williams</author>
    <isbn>978-0985470517</isbn>
    <grade>PreK-G2</grade>
    <cost>$4.25</cost>
    <description>Molly lives in her own little world of make-believe and all things pink. That's because princesses wear pink! Princesses also dress up in pretty things, hang out with fairies…or in Molly's case, her pet dragonfly, and always find a way to be the center of attention. Molly's princess-like life is perfect until a huge disaster spoils her special day and teaches this little lizard there's a lot more to being a princess than looking pretty.</description>
    <ar_points>0.5</ar_points>
    <ar_level>2.7</ar_level>
  </product>
  <product>
    <coverimage><image href="http://longtalepublishing.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/Senorita-Molly_cvr_RGB_72dpi.jpg"/></coverimage>
    <name>Senorita Molly</name>
    <author>Melissa M. Williams</author>
    <isbn>978-1941515594</isbn>
    <grade>PreK-G2</grade>
    <cost>$4.25</cost>
    <description>Molly vive en su pequeño mundo de imaginación, donde todo es color rosa. ¡Y eso es porque todas las princesas se visten de color ROSA! Las princesas tambien se visten muy bonitas y juegan con hadas madrinas. Y en el caso de Molly y su mascota, una libélula, siempre tratan de ser el centro de atención. La vida de Molly, como la de las princesas, parece ser perfecta, hasta que le pasa algo desastrozo que le enseña a esta lagartijita, que hay mucho más sobre las princesas que verse bonitas.</description>
    <ar_points>0.5</ar_points>
    <ar_level>2.7</ar_level>
  </product>
  <product>
    <coverimage><image href="http://longtalepublishing.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/LittleMissMollyColoringBook.jpg"/></coverimage>
    <name>Little Miss Molly Color</name>
    <author>Melissa M. Williams</author>
    <isbn>978-1941515532</isbn>
    <grade>PreK-G2</grade>
    <cost>$0.50</cost>
    <description>Color your way through Little Miss Molly’s world of make-believe, princesses and all things pink! Based on the Little Miss Molly picture books, kids now get to see what this little lizard is up to during each season of the year.</description>
  </product>
  <product>
    <coverimage><image href="http://longtalepublishing.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/10/Shiver_Front-500x637.jpg"/></coverimage>
    <name>Shiver</name>
    <author>Melissa M. Williams</author>
    <isbn>978-1941515754</isbn>
    <grade>PreK-G2</grade>
    <cost>$4.25</cost>
    <description>The underwater world is full of families. Schools of fish, pods of dolphins and swarms of eels swim together in perfect harmony. Trevor dreams of belonging to a family … but he’s a SHARK! No one wants to swim with a tiger shark. But even a shark needs group of friends. Although Trevor is constantly judged by what he looks like on the outside, he never gives up hope of finding a family. His big heart and caring attitude leads him to form the SHIVER of his dreams. Through his experiences and an encounter with a curious sea turtle, Trevor realizes that your family is more than who brought you into the world and that friendships can last a lifetime.</description>
    <ar_points>0.5</ar_points>
    <ar_level>3.1</ar_level>
  </product>
  <product>
    <coverimage><image href="http://longtalepublishing.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/10/0001-e1476712902841.jpg"/></coverimage>
    <name>"i" The Guy Writer's Journal</name>
    <author></author>
    <isbn>978-1941515693</isbn>
    <grade>G3-G5</grade>
    <cost>$2.80</cost>
    <description>iWRITE inspires kids to WRITE their own stories and provides publishing and leadership opportunities to our youth. Since reading and writing go hand in hand, iWRITE encourages readers to use their imagination and communicate through the written word. Join “i” The Guy, the kids’ writing representative, and encourage kids to write for fun, thereby strengthening our youths’ desire to learn and create. Learn more at iWRITE.org.</description>
  </product>
  <product>
    <coverimage><image href="http://longtalepublishing.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/10/0001-e1476712902841.jpg"/></coverimage>
    <name>"i" The Guy Writer's Journal Bilingual</name>
    <author></author>
    <isbn>TBA</isbn>
    <grade>G3-G5</grade>
    <cost>$2.80</cost>
    <description>Bilingual Paperback/Workbook</description>
  </product>
  <product>
    <coverimage><image href="http://longtalepublishing.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/Iggy_NSNR_Book-1.jpg"/></coverimage>
    <name>Iggy the Iguana: New School New Rules</name>
    <author>Melissa M. Williams</author>
    <isbn>978-1941515570</isbn>
    <grade>G3-G5</grade>
    <cost>$2.80</cost>
    <description>New School New Rules is the first book in the Iggy the Iguana Chapter Book Series, which focuses on themes of diversity, friendship and overcoming difficult situations in elementary school. Iggy, the main character, is a role model to kids as he navigates through moving to a new school, making friends and dealing with the school bully. The story allows young readers to relate to different types of characters, while being entertained by the story's fun loving animal humor. The story addresses many useful teaching moments in the 2nd-5th grade classroom.</description>
    <ar_points>3</ar_points>
    <ar_level>4</ar_level>
  </product>
  <product>
    <coverimage><image href="http://longtalepublishing.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/06/IggyTheIguanaCrazyDays.jpg"/></coverimage>
    <name>Iggy the Iguana: Crazy Days of 5th Grade</name>
    <author>Melissa M. Williams</author>
    <isbn>978-1941515648</isbn>
    <grade>G3-G5</grade>
    <cost>$3.00</cost>
    <description>When Iggy's new teacher continues to eat his homework, he realizes his old ways of studying are over. It will take the mind of a creative genius and a lot of make-believe to revitalize Iggy's concentration in class. What started off as a lonely, boring school year missing his best friend Snap Shell, turns into a suspenseful ride that includes a strange encounter with a crab and an unexpected trip to the hospital. With the help of his friends and his little sister's stuffed animals, Iggy discovers a hidden talent that proves he never had a problem after all.</description>
    <ar_points>4</ar_points>
    <ar_level>4.2</ar_level>
  </product>
  <product>
    <coverimage><image href="http://longtalepublishing.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/TurtleTownTheInnerPuka.jpg"/></coverimage>
    <name>Turtle Town: The Inner Puka</name>
    <author>Melissa M. Williams</author>
    <isbn>978-0981805467</isbn>
    <grade>G3-G5</grade>
    <cost>$3.50</cost>
    <description>The first book in the Turtle Town Series, The Inner Puka, is about Snap Shell, a box-shell turtle from Texas, who must find his place among a society of surfing sea turtles along California s southern coast. Snap Shell, the box shell turtle we all loved from the Iggy the Iguana series, has waited his whole life to follow his dream of becoming a real surfer. When his father is transferred to California, Snap gets the chance to embrace the much sought after waves of the West Coast. He faces many challenges, due to his physical differences from the other sea turtles. Good thing he brought his trusty blue flippers! On Snap's journey of becoming the only surfing box shell on the beach, he discovers long hidden secrets that will have the power to either destroy him or truly help him find the inner puka of his soul.</description>
    <ar_points>9</ar_points>
    <ar_level>4.8</ar_level>
  </product>
</productListing>
